In classification tasks we've seen.
在我们看到的分类任务中
We give an image to a CNN and it outputs a label for that entire image.
我们将图像输入到 CNN 中 然后 CNN 为整个图像输出一个标签
But sometimes you want a little more information.
但有时候需要更多信息
Say where the object actually is located in the image and this is called localization.
例如对象在图像中的哪个位置 称之为定位
For example, say you have an image of basketball players and you want to
例如 假设有一张包含多位篮球运动员的图像
identify the player that has possession of the basketball at this time.
你想知道目前拿着球的运动员是谁
To complete this task,
要完成此任务
you need to locate and identify the ball and the person that's holding it.
你需要定位并识别篮球和握着篮球的运动员
Localization has been used in a variety of safety applications too.
各种安全应用也用到了定位技术
For example and baby monitors that check to see if a baby is safely in a crib.
例如 婴儿监视器会检查婴儿是否安全地位于婴儿床里
And localization is even in
甚至安全驾驶应用
safe driving applications in which a camera checks
也用到了定位技术
to see if a driver is distracted or not
摄像头会查看驾驶员在车辆中的位置
by looking at the location of a driver in a vehicle and
以及眼睛 手机和周围其他物品的位置
the location of their eyes cell phone and other items around them.
判断驾驶员是否分神了
Localization is important for any application that
对于任何需要查看两个或多个对象的距离的应用
relies on looking at the proximity of two or more objects.
定位技术都很重要
So let's look at a simple Localization example.
我们来看一个简单的定位示例 这是一张猫的图像
This image of a cat, in addition to labeling this image
除了将该图像标记为猫之外
as a cat we also want to locate the cat in this image.
我们还需要定位该图像中的猫
The typical way of doing this is by drawing a bounding box around that cat.
典型方法是在该猫周围画一个边界框
This box can be thought of as a collection of coordinates that define the box,
这个方框可以看做定义该方框的一系列坐标
X and Y which could be the center of the box and W and H,
(x,y) 可以是方框的中心
the width and height of the box.
w 和 h 分别表示方框的宽和高
To find these values we can use a lot of
要计算这些值 我们可以使用典型分类 CNN
the same structure as in a typical classification CNN.
用到的很多相同结构
One way to perform localization is to first put a given image through
一种定位方式是首先将给定图像
a series of convolutional and pooling layers and create a feature vector for that image.
传入一系列卷积层和池化层 并为该图像创建一个特征向量
You keep the same fully-connected layers to perform classification and you add
保留相同的全连接层进行分类
another fully connected layer attached to
然后在特征向量之后添加另一个全连接层
the feature vector whose job is to predict the location and size of a bounding box.
目的是预测边界框的位置和大小
I'll call these the bounding box coordinates.
我将称其为边界框坐标
In this one CNN,
在这个 CNN 中
we have one output path whose job is to produce a class for the object pictured in
有一个输出路径 作用是为图像中的对象生成类别
an image and another who's job is to produce the bounding box coordinates for the object.
另一个输出路径的作用是生成该对象的边界框坐标
In this case we're assuming that the input image not only has an associated true label,
在这个示例中 我们假设输入图像不仅具有相关的真实标签
but that it also has a true bounding box.
而且具有真实的边界框
This way we can train our network by comparing
这样我们可以通过
the predicted and true values for both the classes and bounding boxes.
对比类别和边界框的预测值和真实值训练网络
Now we know how to use something like cross
我们已经知道如何使用交叉熵损失等
entropy loss to measure the performance of a classification model.
衡量分类模型的性能
Cross entropy operates on probabilities with values between zero and one.
交叉熵适合概率值在 0 和 1 之间的模型
But for the bounding box we need something different.
但是对于边界框 我们需要其他损失函数
A function that measures the error between our predicted
这种函数能够衡量
bounding box and a true bounding box.
预测边界框和真实边界框之间的误差
Next you'll see what kinds of loss functions are
接下来 你将了解对于这样的回归问题
appropriate for a regression problem like this,
什么样的损失函数比较合适
that compares quantities instead of class scores.
能够对比数量 而不是类别得分